Guide to the Joel B. Levinson Photographs, 1950-2006 AIS.2015.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Joel B. Levinson Photographs
1950-2006
1980-1999
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Levinson, Joel
Nega, Susan L.
AIS.2015.01
5.25 Linear Feet (7 boxes, 1 oversize folder)
Joel B. Levinson, an independent photographer in Pittsburgh, Pa., who worked primarily in the 1980s and 1990s, produced numerous calendars, postcards, and photographic essays highlighting the people, events, and structures of the city under the name Pittsburghscape. The collection is comprised of approximately 7,000 items and includes photographic prints, slides, negatives, positives, and manuscript materials related to Levinson's photography of the Pittsburgh region that showcase the diversity of his subject matter.
Biography
Joel B. Levinson was born in Pittsburgh, Pa., in 1934, where he remained for most of his life. His varied career included working as a businessman, an engineer, industrial appraiser, and a photographer. After graduating from Carnegie Tech in 1956, Levinson married Toba Goldenfeld in 1957. In 1958 he began working for Levinson Steel, the nationally-known company founded in 1902 by his grandfather, where he remained until the company was sold in 1983. In the late 1970s, Levinson began extensively photographing the structures and people of the Pittsburgh region.
After publishing his first photographic essay with Lynn Johnson in 1984, entitled "Pittsburgh Moments," Levinson's interest in documenting numerous aspects of Pittsburgh increased to a self-described "love affair with the city." Around this time, he began producing calendars, postcards, and prints of the Pittsburgh region under the name Pittsburghscape. Throughout the 1980s and 1990s, Levinson, alongside assistant Susan Nega, photographed Pittsburgh's landscape, events, attractions, and residents. Levinson and Nega jointly managed their commercial photography business, J.B. Jeffers Ltd.
In 1991, Levinson released another photographic essay, "Pittsburgh: Views between the Rivers," which he updated and expanded in 1996 under the new title "Pittsburgh: Views into the 21st Century." In 2000, he moved to Boulder, Co., to be closer to family. Levinson revised the essay again in 2004, including additional photographs and modifying the text to reflect the changing city which he still photographed when visiting. "Pittsburgh: Views in the 21st Century" was Levinson's last homage to the city he dearly loved. Levinson's passion for photography was passed along to his children and grandchildren, many of whom have become photographers as well. He passed away on October 26, 2007 in Boulder.
Susan Nega was born in Pittsburgh and graduated from Penn Hills High School. She attended the University of Pittsburgh where she obtained a degree in Liberal Arts with a focus mainly on photography and film studies (class of 1989). With a love of photography, working in the darkroom, and exploring the city, she went to work for Joel Levinson at J.B. Jeffers Ltd., a publishing company specializing in images of Pittsburgh's cityscapes, neighborhoods, attractions and events, and people. Joel's mentoring provided new ways of seeing the city, its people, and capturing what is special in everyday surroundings. After 10 years at J.B. Jeffers Ltd., publishing calendars, postcards, and a book of the city, Susan (and her husband) decided to move to New York City. She worked for a short time at the publisher Fotofolio Inc., which was also a publisher of books, postcards, notecards, and posters of fine art and photography.
Arrangement
The organization for the Levinson photographs has been kept largely in its original order, with some shifting to bring items from the same events back together. The collection is organized by events or themes, although there is no chronological order. Images and materials relating to Levinson's publications are primarily contained in boxes 5 through 7.
Previous Citation
Joel B. Levinson Photographs, 1950-2006, AIS.2015.01, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Scope and Content Notes
The Joel B. Levinson Photographs is comprised of approximately 7,000 items and includes photographic prints, slides, negatives, positives, and manuscript materials related to his photography of the Pittsburgh region. Items date from 1968 to 2006 with the bulk of the collection dating from the 1980s and 1990s.
Levinson loved to document his hometown and was a frequent fixture at cultural and sporting events such as the Pittsburgh Marathon, Vintage Grand Prix, Three Rivers Arts Festival, and Three Rivers Regatta. He was particularly struck by the Pittsburgh skyline and would return to the same locations many times over the course of his career to capture Pittsburgh's evolving landscapes and built environments.
While Levinson is the primary photographer, the work of Levinson's assistant (Susan Nega), his sons (Jeff and Drew), along with John Beale, Leo Hsu, and Norman Schumm are also included.
Related Material
Levinson Steel Company Records, 1926-1985, MSS 1042, Rauh Jewish Archives, Thomas and Katherine Detre Library and Archives, Senator John Heinz History Center
Acquisition Information
Gift of Jeffery B., Toba, Eric, Drew and Mark Levinson on March 2015.
Slides (Photographs); Negatives (Photographic); Shadyside (Pittsburgh, Pa.); North Side (Pittsburgh, Pa.); South Side (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Mount Washington (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Oakland (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Kennywood Park (Pa.); Landscape photography; Pittsburgh (Pa.) -- Pictorial works; Photographs; Buildings -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh -- Photographs; Pittsburgh (Pa.); Neighborhoods -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh -- Photographs; Pittsburgh (Pa.) -- Aerial photographs; Cityscapes; Skyline; Pittsburgh Steelers (Football team); Duquesne Incline (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Fallingwater (Pa.); Point State Park; Kennywood Park; Levinson, Joel; Heinz Memorial Chapel (University of Pittsburgh); McConnell's Mill State Park (Pa.); Three Rivers Arts Festival (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Pittsburgh Center for the Arts (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Three Rivers Regatta (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Gateway Clipper (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Thrift Drug Bike Classic; Schenley Park (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Vintage Grand Prix (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Pittsburgh Marathon; University of Pittsburgh; Carnegie-Mellon University; Phipps Conservatory; Carnegie Museum of Natural History; Cathedral of Learning (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Pittsburghscape
- Race for the Cure, May 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- University of Pittsburgh, Heinz Chapel, February 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Downtown Pittsburgh, January 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- East Liberty, February 1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Squirrel Hill, February 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Southside and Skyline, January 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Skyline and fireworks, July 4, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- South Side Hills, June 1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- South Side Dock and Slopes, May 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Pittsburgh Presentation (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Great Race, September 1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Carnegie Science Center, May 1998 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Toba Getting a Tattoo and Three Rivers Arts Festival, June 1998 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- View from Bigelow Boulevard, June 1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- University of Pittsburgh, February 1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Carnegie Mellon University, February 1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- View of the Point, September 1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Light-Up Bridges, August 1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Carnegie Mellon University and Shadyside, August 1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Three Rivers Regatta and Shadyside Arts Festival, August 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Skyline, July 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Thrift Drug Bike Classic, June 1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Steelers vs. Broncos, January 11, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Steelers Pep Rally, January 9, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Mansion on Fifth Avenue, DoubleTree Hotel, and Davio restaurant, January 1998 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- PPG Place Wintergarden, December 1997 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- McConnells Mill State Park, June 1995 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- "The Temptations" Filming, September 1998 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Pittsburgh at Sunset, September 1998 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Sunnyledge Hotel on Fifth Avenue, January 1998 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Mattress Factory, January 1998 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Downtown Building Implosion, May 25, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Bike Classic, June 1997 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Oakland and Carnegie Mellon University, June 1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Carnegie Mellon University, January 1998 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Oakland, February 1998 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- University of Pittsburgh, September 1996 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- A Fair in the Park, September 1996 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Frozen Pond, March 1996 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Schenley Playground, September 1996 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- North Side, February 1996 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Downtown in Winter, January 1996 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Trampoline, May 1997 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Washington, PA, May 1997 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- South Side Slopes, May 1997 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Race for the Cure, May 1997 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Downtown sights, March 1997 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Station Square, March 1997 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Oakland, December 1995 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Aerial Views of Pittsburgh, August-September 1994 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- "Pittsburgh: Views Between the Rivers" slides for publication, ca. 1980s (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Pittsburgh Sights and Attractions, ca. 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Skyline (Box 2, Folder 3)
- South Side views, ca. 1983-1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Pittsburgh Center for the Arts and City, ca. 1986-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Building Details, ca. 1988-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Vintage Grand Prix, July 1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Bike Classic, May 21, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- CBS Morning Show, August 4, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Aerial views of Pittsburgh, September 1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Schenley Ice Rink with Paul Wylie (Olympian), February 1992 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Cathedral of Learning, University of Pittsburgh, ca. 1970-1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- University of Pittsburgh, ca. 1983-1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Downtown Details (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Strip District, May-June 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Schenley Sledding, January 1992 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- North Side and Skyline, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Downtown Skyline and Buildings, ca. 1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Events in Pittsburgh, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Skyline, ca. 1977-1989 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Duquesne Incline, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Downtown Details and Sights, ca. 1980s (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Israel Day Parade, May 1986 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Regatta, August 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Arts Festival, June 1990 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Pittsburgh Skyline and Fireworks, June-October 1991 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Fireworks and Christmas tree (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Skyline, ca. 1980s (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Gateway Clipper Fleet and Regatta, ca. 1987 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- South Side Flats and Pittsburgh Buildings, ca. 1980s (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Downtown Sights, ca. 1980s (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Horne's Christmas Tree, December 1984 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Mills and Industry, ca. 1978-1990 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Three Rivers Stadium, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Point State Park fountain and Duquesne Incline, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Kennywood, ca. 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Skyline from North Shore, June 1991 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Thrift Drug Bike Classic, May 1991 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Monongahela Valley area and Rankin, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Idlewild Park, ca. 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Marathon, Syria Mosque, Cathedral of Learning, and Point State Park fountain, April-May 1991 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Pittsburgh Center for the Arts, Frick Art and Historical Society and Clayton, 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Polish Hill and Bloomfield, ca. 1986-1990 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- North Side, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- South Side, 1984-1988 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Colonial Weekend, May 1993 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Bike Classic, May 1994 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Downtown, May 1993 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- All-Star Game, July 1994 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- The Carnegie, September 1991 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Phipps Conservatory, December 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Arts Festival, June 1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Pittsburgh city sights and holiday parade, November 1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Christmas Storytelling - Oxford Building, November 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Light Up Night, November 1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Shadyside Arts and Three Rivers Arts, August 1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Steelers vs. Buffalo, January 1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Winter, December 1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Oakland, December 1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Filming Inspector Gadget, September 1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Sparkle Night at DoubleTree Hotel, November 24, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Arts Festival, June 1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Pittsburgh Sunrise from Greenfield, November 1995 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- City from North Side, Warhol Museum and Toba, October 1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- National Aviary, October 1995 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Flowers and Toba, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Steelers Game, January 1998 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Homestead, January 1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- McDonalds, Forbes Field Wall, and More, October 1990 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- PNC Park (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Bike Classic, May 1991 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- 4th of July, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Pittsburgh Zoo Lights, January 1998 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Downtown and Heinz Sign, January-March 1996 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Movie Set- Town, September 1996 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- The Point from West End at Sunset, October 1993 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Schenley Park and Phipps Conservatory, December 1993 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Christmas Downtown and Horne's Tree, December 1993 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Pittsburgh Events (Box 3, Folder 29)
- The Carnegie, ca. 1984-1990 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- City from Greenfield, October 1993 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- View from Cathedral of Learning and other Pittsburgh Sights, ca. 1986-1995 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- University of Pittsburgh and Phipps Conservatory, 1984-1990 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Oakland, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Downtown, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Benedum Center and Ballet, November 1995 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Arts Festival, June 1996 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Oakland, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 3, Folder 38)
- South Side and River, June 1996 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Skylines (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Pittsburgh Sights, ca. 1983-1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Downtown, October 1993 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Carnegie Mellon University Postcard, ca. 1984-1992 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Oakland, May 1992 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Carnegie Mellon University, ca. 1984-1996 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- View from North Side and hot air balloons, ca. 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Rowing Regatta, September 1990 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- City Christmas, November 1990 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Birmingham Bridge- South Side, July 1992 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Great Race, September 1995 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Regatta, August 1995 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Pittsburgh from North, ca. 1989-1993 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Sunset Skyline, September 1993 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Parade, March 1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Steelers fans and Penguins game, ca. 1980s (Box 4, Folder 2)
- WQED, Good Morning America, and AIDS Quilt, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Arts Festival, ca. 1978-1989 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Great Race, ca. 1980s (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Carnegie Mellon University Buggy Race, April 1990 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Vintage Grand Prix from Flagstaff Hill, July 1999 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Summer Concert, June 1986 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Pittsburgh Marathon, May 1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Downtown Buildings, Piano, Fallingwater, and More, ca. 1970s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 10)
- South Side Slopes, Sculpture Court and Christmas tree, ca. 1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Jewish Community Center and Pittsburgh Marathon, May 1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Homestead, Pittsburgh Marathon and bike race, May 1992 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Children's Festival, May 1992 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Kennywood - Rotor and Cannonball Man, ca. 1989 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Bike Classic, Vintage Grand Prix and Squirrel Hill, May-July 1992 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- 4th of July, Regatta and City Sights, July-August 1992 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Ligonier and Soergel Orchards, October 1992 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Boats and Downtown, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Pirates Game, August 1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Great Race, September 1992 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Boats on Three Rivers, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Buildings and skyline, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 23)
- South Side Church and Downtown, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Chatham area (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Widelux Panorama (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Regatta, August 1990 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- South Side Train Track and Downtown, ca. 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Strip District, October 1991 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Sledding at Chatham and Skyline, January 1992 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Oakland in Winter and St. Patrick's Day Parade, January-March 1992 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- University of Pittsburgh from South Side, April 1992 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Carnegie Mellon University Fair, April 1992 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Industrial Landscapes, ca. 1977-1991 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Fallingwater and Surrounding Area, ca. 1986 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Kennywood and Idlewild Amusement Parks, ca. 1991 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Squirrel Hill and Shadyside, ca. 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Bloomfield, Lawrenceville, Greenfield, and Pittsburgh Neighborhoods, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 38)
- The Point, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Downtown, Oakland, and Pittsburgh Sights and Events, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 40)
- PPG Place, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Barge and Downtown, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Pittsburgh Sights and Events, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Published, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Carnegie Mellon University Buildings, Buggy race, and Downtown, ca. 1983-1999 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Regatta Balloons, August 1993 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Pittsburgh Presentation, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Fireworks and Downtown Details, ca. 1990s (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Downtown and Steelers Game, ca. 1990s (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Downtown, Bridges, and the Carnegie (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Pittsburgh and West Coast, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Downtown, Cathedral of Learning, and Carnegie Mellon University, ca. 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Downtown and Oakland, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Pittsburgh Sights and Events, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Carnegie Science Center, Heinz Field and PNC Park, ca. 2000s (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Downtown Bridges and Skyline (Box 5, Folder 3)
- The Pennsylvanian Rotunda, Heinz Hall, and Downtown, ca. 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- The Point and Cathedral of Learning, ca. 1990s (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Downtown Fireworks (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Aerial Views of Oakland, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- University of Pittsburgh, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Light Up Day, Parade, and Night, November 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- City from North Side, July 1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- West End Bridge and the Point, June 1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- South Side Church and Oakland, June 1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Shadyside, June 1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Folk Festival and Boats, May-July 1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- McKees Rocks Jewish Cemetery, 1975, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Shadyside and Oakland, June 1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Downtown and Industrial Landscapes, July 1994 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Vintage Grand Prix, 1983, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- South Side Slopes, July 1994 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- City and South Side Street, August 1994 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- South Side Slopes, August 1994 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Mt. Washington, August 1994 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Three Rivers Stadium (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Trampoline Girls, July 1997 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Christmas tree and Carnegie Museum of Art (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Mr. Ribbs - Squirrel Hill, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Benedum Center Ballet (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Slides for Publication, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Slides for Publication, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Empty Bowls Event (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Portola Mural, California (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Fallingwater and Ohiopyle Prints for Publication and Postcard, ca. 1989 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Downtown Fireworks, ca. 1998 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Slides for Postcard Publications, ca. 1990s (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Slides for Calendar Publications, ca. 1990s (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Slides for 1998 Calendar Publication, ca. 1990s (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Slides for 1999 Calendar Publication, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Pirates and Steelers Prints for Publication (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Slides for Publication, ca. 1980s (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Downtown Bridges (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Downtown Positives (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Downtown Prints (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Downtown and Back Cover for "Pittsburgh: Views Between the Rivers" (Box 5, Folder 43)
- PPG Plaza at Night for Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
- People, Places and Events around Pittsburgh, ca. 1980s-1990s (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Three Rivers Arts Festival, June 1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Dan Kamin - Mime, September 1990 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Cornfield, August 1991 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- A Fair in the Park, September 1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- University of Pittsburgh, November 1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- New Kensington in Fall, October 1994 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Fort Ligonier Days, October 1994 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Carnegie Mellon University Fair, April 1992 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Lemont and City, June 1994 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- House and Architectural Details, ca. 1993-1995 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Aerial Views of Oakland and More, August 1994 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- PPG Building Detail, June 1994 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Downtown, November 1994 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Bob Painting Town Quarters, March 1986 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Duquesne Incline Restoration, August 1994 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Carnegie Museum, January 1995 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Kids Photos, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Pittsburgh Changes, ca. 1950-1985 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Carnegie Tech, ca. 1955-1959 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Pittsburgh Buildings and Roads, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Parade, June 1993 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- South Side, May 1998 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Carnegie Mellon University and Downtown, June 1998 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Great Race, September 1998 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Downtown, September 1998 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Skyline (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Skyline, April 1994 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Labor Day Parade, September 1997 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Holiday Parade, Downtown, and Three Rivers Regatta (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Aerial Views, September 1995 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Skyline and Fog (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Light Up Festivities, November 1994 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Lights at Phipps Conservatory and Ft. Pitt bridge (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Light Up Night, November 1996 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Skyline and Vintage Car, July 1997 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Regatta and Cathedral of Learning (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Bridges and Downtown, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Regatta Balloons, October 1993 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- CBS morning show in Downtown, August 4, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Duquesne Incline for Publication (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Fireworks, September 1991 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- The Point (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Chaco Canyon, NM, Boulder, CO and more Southwest, ca. 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Downtown Prints and Negative for Publication (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Inter Negs for publication (Box 6, Folder 47-50)
- Inter Negs for Publication, including for "Pittsburgh: Views Between the Rivers" (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Copy Negatives for Publication (Box 6, Folder 52)
- The Point and Bridges (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Prints for "Pittsburgh: Views into the 21st Century," 1996 Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Slides and Negatives for 1996 and 2004 Publications, ca. 1970s-1990s (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
- Personal Copy of "Pittsburgh: Views into the 21st Century", 1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)